I don't usually meet women
as beautiful as you
at a tech convention.
Aw, that's very sweet.
And you were definitely
the hottest guy there.
(chuckles) Thank you.
Although, to be fair,
being the hottest guy at a tech
convention is kind of like...
well, being the hottest guy
at a tech convention.
Although, once, I saw
Justin Timberlake
at a Microsoft party.
Lady boner! (laughs)
Yes, he did bring sexy back
to Windows 8.
So, you said
you work for Google?
That's right, in the
modeling department.
Oh, that's awesome.
Like graphic rendering
and 3-D imaging?
More like pointing.
"New from Google,
confusing tech crap."
Oh, so you're, like,
a model-model?
Yep. You can't spell
Google without "ogle."
Can you?
No, you can't.
But being a model at tech shows
isn't what I really want to do.
I just do it to
pay the bills.
Oh, I get it.
What's your ultimate goal?
I want to help
teach people to read.
Oh, that's noble.
So, you want to be a teacher.
No, I want to be
the next Vanna White.
(giggles)
Oh, you're serious.
Yeah. I mean, she
has an amazing job,
she wears amazing outfits
and she has amazing hair.
Somebody needs to buy
a new, amazing adjective.
You can't buy adjectives.
You can only buy vowels.
Right.
Only vowels.
Well, I owe you
another drink.
"O." "K."
(under breath): Certainly won't
be any "I" in "U" tonight.
Wow, that girl is gorgeous.
Yeah, she's a model.
We don't really
have a connection.
She's not very bright.
I think she thinks
Silicon Valley is the place
where women go
to get a boob job.
Oh, you want
intellectual stimulation.
Uh, why don't you
watch an episode of Nova
while you're
banging her brains out?
No, I'm gonna go tell her
it's not gonna work out.
Well, if you don't want her,
can I have her?
Oh, sure, let's change shirts.
Maybe she won't notice.
Oh, she's that dumb?
Great.
WOMAN:
Walden!
Look, a seagu...
(screams)
Oh, my God.
Wait.
We didn't switch shirts yet.
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Ah.
♪ Men.
♪ Two and a Half Men 11x09 ♪
Numero Uno Accidente Lawyer
Original Air Date on December 5, 2013
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Hey, what's going on?
I was cleaning out my closet
and I found a box
of Jake's old stuff.
Aw, that's sweet.
Who's Jake?
My son. Y-Your cousin.
Oh, right.
Oh, and how did he die?
Oh, no, h-he's not dead.
He's in the Army.
Huh.
Ah. Nice bong.
Guess he's not
fighting the war on drugs.
No, that-that is
a hummingbird feeder.
He made it in art class.
And in shop class,
I made a train whistle.
(imitates whistle):
Weed, weed!
No, no, seriously.
Uh, one summer,
back in high school,
he and his friends
got into bird watching.
They'd spend all day
out in the woods, and they'd...
they'd come back laughing and...
Oh, God, I'm an idiot.
Don't worry.
All parents are idiots.
My mom used to think I was
locked in the bathroom all day
with an electric toothbrush.
(buzzes)
My first wife was always
using her electric tooth...
God, I am an idiot.
Oh, look at this.
One of his old report cards.
Oh, you can still see where
he tried to change his grades.
Yeah, he changed the C's.
To D's.
Yeah. That was the year
his bus got a little shorter.
But, you know,
in his defense,
his teacher changed
that year, too.
She went from C's to D's.
Is this how you're
spending your night?
Oh, no, no. Later,
I'm going to shave my back.
Oh, actually,
if you're not busy...
I am. And so are you.
I'm gonna get a drink.
Where's Walden?
Oh, he had to take his date
to the hospital.
Ooh, what are they pulling out,
and from where?
No, it-it's nothing like that.
She was looking up at the sky
and she fell off the deck.
High?
No.
Drunk?
Model?
Yeah.
♪ Men. ♪
How you feeling?
I'm all right.
Uh, well, we need
to fill out this paperwork.
So, uh, first name, Nadine.
This is awkward.
I don't know your last name.
It's H-O-R-E.
H-O-R-E.
Like "hooray"?
No, like "whore."
You think I
should change it?
No, be proud.
I'm sure you come from
a long line of... Hores.
Uh, any relatives
I can call?
No, they're
all back east.
I'm the only Hore
in Los Angeles.
Agree to disagree.
Emergency contacts.
Okay, so no family.
Uh, friends? Roommates?
Anyone you've gone on
more than one date with?
Not really.
I live alone.
I've only been in L.A.
a couple weeks.
The only men in my
life are you and Frank.
Oh, all right.
How do I get a hold of Frank?
He's a pig.
(chuckles) He's a pig,
you're a Hore.
No one's judging.
No, he's my pet pig.
My little frankfurter.
A pig.
Does he sleep
in a blanket?
Yeah, he totally
hogs the covers.
(laughs) Hogs. Good one.
Never mind.
Uh, what about medications?
Love 'em.
No, I-I think they mean
"are you taking any now?"
Oh, let's see, there's
plaxitril for my depression,
zaxaprin for my anxiety,
dilapamin for my
insomnia, and clodex
for my occasional
bouts of rage.
No one likes
an angry Hore.
(indistinct conversations)
(sighs) Why didn't you tell me
we were going to a gay bar?
'Cause if I told you,
you wouldn't have come.
Yes, I would. I just
would've dressed better.
And just to be clear,
you do know I'm
not gay, right?
I don't think you're gay.
I-I mean, do I know guys
that act less gay
that have sex
with other guys? Sure.
But I know
you're straight.
So, why bring me here?
Look around this room.
See all the women here?
Yeah.
Well, some of them
are gay. Those are mine.
The rest are straight.
Some of those
are mine, too.
And everyone who's left
is gonna be drunk and horny
by the end of the night
and looking for someone who
doesn't think vaginas are yucky.
Oh, oh, you mean me.
(high-pitched):
Yay.
(deeper voice):
I mean, yay.
Okay, be careful.
Mm.
Watch your leg.
You smell so good.
Thank you.
Let's see how you taste.
Okay. All right.
I see the painkillers
have kicked in.
Oh, they sure did.
Right now, you could
do anything to me
and I wouldn't remember.
Did I wink?
'Cause I was trying to wink.
Okay, let's-let's get
you on the couch, huh?
Hey, let's get you on Nadine.
Oh, okay.
All right, fine.
Let's... just rest.
Thank you so much
for taking care of me.
Well, you have a broken leg.
You don't have
any family or friends
and you live on the fourth floor
of a building with no elevator.
So, I couldn't just
leave you on the street.
Could I?
You're handsome.
(grunts)
Yeah.
You're... drooling.
I'm gonna get
you some food.
All right, but I have
certain dietary constrictions.
I don't eat wheat, dairy,
or anything with a face.
Although...
I would make
an exception for you.
So, you're here
with your niece?
Uh, yeah, she just recently
came out of the closet
and she's painfully shy.
Oh. Mm-hmm.
Now, that's what I
call breast-feeding.
She's, uh, still trying
to find her gay legs.
Ah. Well, she's lucky she has
an uncle who's found his.
(sighs) No, I'm straight.
Why does everybody
think I'm gay?
Oh, that is way too tart.
Um, so, Paula,
what do you do?
I'm an investment banker.
Oh, wow. Oh, okay,
maybe you can answer a question
I've always had.
Mm-hmm?
What's the penalty
for early withdrawal?
Well, uh, that depends.
How big is your deposit?
Oh, interest is rising.
You know, the longer
you keep it in,
the bigger your reward.
Sometimes,
the market collapses
and there's nothing
you can do about it.
Uh, wait. Are-are we
doing sexual innuendo
or are you asking for
free financial advice?
Why can't it be both?
You know,
if you're interested,
I've got a Malibu
beach house.
Oh. Well, if you're interested,
I've got very loose morals.
(high-pitched):
Yay.
(deeper):
I mean, yay.
(chuckling):
Wow.
That was amazing.
(laughs)
Uh-huh.
Wait, it wasn't?
'Cause I can do better.
No, you were great.
Oh, thank God,
'cause I can't do better.
Oh.
But there is something I
probably should've told you
before we slept together.
Oh, God, husband or herpes?
Uh...
Well, there was
another guy. Paul.
Paul. Paula.
That must have been confusing...
Very, yeah. Um...
You see, for the first
40 years of my life,
I was a man named Paul.
Wow.
You don't look... 40.
♪ Men. ♪
So, so, you were a guy?
With, you know,
an Adam's apple
and facial hair,
and the whole kit
and kaboodle?
Yep, I had a kit
and two kaboodles.
So, so, how did
you get that?
I mean, did you
have to get a donor?
'Cause I've never
seen that box
to check on
a driver's license.
Actually, uh, I-I... I
donated my own organ.
You see, what they do, they
take your penis, all right?
They slice it right down the middle...
Oh! La la la la la la la la la.
Okay, I'll-I'll
spare you the details
on what happened
to my balls.
Well, I know
what just happened to mine.
Look, I-I know I should
have told you earlier.
I just didn't want to scare
you away. I really like you.
Oh, and I like you. I mean,
we have a lot in common.
Clearly more than I realized.
Maybe it's best if I go.
Oh, no, no, don't do.
You sure?
Yeah, yeah, no, I like you.
I'm just, I'm trying
to process this whole thing.
I mean, for instance,
there's no chance
it'll grow back, right?
What, like-like a
salamander's tail?
No. Uh-uh.
So one day you're not gonna,
you know, sneeze real hard
and suddenly
I'm dating a dude?
Alan, I am as much a woman
as you've ever dated.
But if you're not okay with this, it's...
No, no, no, you know what?
I am not going to let one
little thing come between us.
Oh, it wasn't little.
Okay, uh, Paula, bit of,
uh, relationship advice?
Uh, no guy likes to hear
that his girlfriend
had a bigger penis than he does.
You're right.
(chuckles)
I'm sorry.
(sneezes)
Sorry.
Gesundheit.
Morning.
Oh great, we're
out of bacon.
Whoa.
We're out of naked
Heidi Klum.
Damn.
That's Frank. He belongs
to my date Nadine.
Alan told me about her.
That's the model
you took to the emergency room.
Twice. She calls it our
"special place."
It's the worst date of my life.
Is her mouth broken?
No.
So what's the problem?
The problem is,
we have no connection.
How can I be attracted
to a woman's body
if I'm not attracted
to her mind?
Sounds kind of gay,
but all right.
Hey, Walden.
Jenny.
Zippy.
Just a heads-up, there's a girl
asleep on the couch.
Don't worry,
I know the drill, boss.
Give her 500 bucks,
pat her down for silverware
and throw her in a taxi.
What?
Sorry. Charlie flashback.
Morning.
(snorts)
Whoa!
That's a pig.
Whoa! That's a leech.
Long story, crazy night.
(scoffs) Pig or no pig,
not as crazy as mine.
100 bucks says mine beats yours.
I had sex with a woman
who used to be a man.
And we have a winner.
What, really?
I can't believe
that you would...
Well, ah, then again, it's you.
Hey, hey, say what you want,
but she really
knows her way around a man.
It's like climbing Mount Everest
with a really good Sherpa.
Yeah, but you don't
shtup the Sherpa.
How did it work?
Like, where did it... go?
Oh, that's easy.
See, what they do is,
they slice the penis
down the middle...
Oh. La la la la la.
La la la la la.
NADINE:
Walden?
Is there somewhere
I can take a bath?
Oh, yeah, upstairs.
Here, I'll help you.
No.
I will never get out of here
if I don't start
to do things on my own.
Unless you don't
want me to leave.
Top of the stairs, on the left.
That girl is really messed up.
The only thing wrong with mine
is the occasional
five o'clock shadow.
You know, I've got to say,
Alan, you going out
with a post-op transgendered
person without any judgment--
very enlightened.
Oh, thank you.
And you should see her boobs.
(cell phone chiming)
You're getting a call
from a "Hore?"
Hi, Nadine.
You got... you got it
stuck where?
Don't move, I'll
be right there.
Nadine got her boot
caught in the banister.
Excuse me.
NADINE:
Never mind, I got it.
(loud thud)
Oh no.
500 bucks in cab fare,
and he'd be out of this.
I can't believe how easily
we agreed on a movie.
I know, men and women aren't
usually on the same page.
Oh, oh, here it is.
Uh, theater three, Julia Roberts
in Hashtag: I Love You.
Listen, I'm gonna get a soda.
Do you want something?
Oh, sure. Uh, oh, let me see
what I'm in the mood for.
Oh, uh, want to split a hot dog?
Mmm.
Oh, I am so sorry.
It's fine.
Hi. Uh, can we have
two Diet Cokes
and a hot dog, please?
Oh, uh...
Don't worry, I got it.
Okay, but
I'm used to paying.
This is...
this is so weird.
Sorry, just, you know, old
habits from when I was Paul.
I-I hope you're
okay with that.
I think it's pretty clear
that I'm willing
to work around things
in this relationship.
Well, I appreciate it,
because I'm having a
great time with you.
Oh, well, so am I.
Mm-hmm?
Uh, but going forward,
you're gonna have to learn
to embrace my masculinity
and, you know, accept the fact
that I'm the-- thank you--
man in this relationship.
Oh, it's chilly in here.
Oh, here. Take my jacket.
Oh. Cozy.
(slap, thud, knock)
(slap, thud,
knock)
Who's there?
It's just me, silly.
Is everything all right?
You've taken
such good care of me,
I thought it was time for me
to take good care of you.
Oh, that's not necessary.
Why not?
We could play doctor.
Haven't you
seen enough doctors?
Okay, we could play
Pat and Vanna.
The clue is "things
people do naked."
Okay, Nadine, just stop.
What's wrong?
(sighs) We're not
gonna sleep together.
Are you saying
that you don't
want any of this?
"N," and I'd like
to buy five O's.
Look, we-we just don't click.
I can't believe
you led me on. Ooh.
Led you on? I let you in.
I was trying to help you.
Do I look like I need your help?
♪ Men. ♪
(phone rings)
Yeah? No, I'm not
doing anything.
Seriously?
I know, I know.
I should say something.
No, no, it's fine.
I'll come over after the movie.
(scoffs)
He should go now.
What's that?
Shh!
Just ignore him. People
can only make you angry
with your permission.
Right. But if he opens his mouth
again, I will get the usher.
(chuckles)
I got my review.
Hashtag piece of crap.
Shh!
All right, you know
what? That's it.
Oh, wait, oh, no, no, no,
Let me do this.
Alan, Alan, you don't have to do this.
Yes, I do. I'm the man
and this is what a man does.
Now, hold my Jujubes.
Uh, excuse me, sir?
What?
Um, uh, we're all
trying to watch the movie
and I don't know if you
remember what the, uh,
the little cartoon
popcorn bucket said,
but "silence is golden."
Oh, yeah? What are you
gonna do about it?
Uh, well, I
just did it
and it didn't seem
very effective, so...
Go sit down.
Okay, you know what?
Why don't you sit down?
Ow.
What the... What...
I'm sorry.
Don't apologize.
Paula? Hashtag
I love you.
♪ Men. ♪
I thought this relationship
was going somewhere.
Okay, seriously? The only place
this relationship is going
is the emergency room.
I thought this was
something special.
I thought I was going to be
Mrs. Nadine Hore-Schmidt.
Okay, this is crazy.
I mean, we wouldn't have
gotten past the first date
if you hadn't
fallen off my deck.
That's right.
I did fall off your deck.
I'll be sure to mention that
to my lawyer.
Your lawyer?
You heard me.
Perhaps you've seen his picture
on the side of the bus?
You don't get to be
the numero uno accidente lawyer
by accident.
Come on, Frank.
(Frank snorts)
Take care of yourself, Frank.
What's going on?
Oh, Nadine is going to sue me
because I won't sleep with her.
Oh, that's a thing?
Don't tell Alan.
(tires squealing)
(crash)
Oh, that can't be.
(cell phone chiming)
Hi, Nadine.
I'll be right there.
Nadine got hit by a bus.
Back to our special place.
♪ Men. ♪
What do you want to watch?
I know someone
wants to watch Babe again.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man